<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Facebook</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Jelszó</string>
    <string name="login">Bejelentkezés</string>
    <string name="registration">Regisztráció</string>
    <string name="register">Regisztráció</string>
    <string name="user_first_name">Keresztnév</string>
    <string name="user_second_name">Vezetéknév</string>
    <string name="email_address">Email</string>
    <string name="password_again">Jelszó újra</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Telefonszám</string>
    <string name="address">Cím</string>
    <string name="account_type">Fiók típusa</string>
    <string name="customer">Magánszemély</string>
    <string name="seller">Oldal</string>
    <string name="cancel">Mégse</string>

    <string name="person_name">Név</string>
    <string name="text_placeholder">Leírás</string>
    <string name="add_friend">Add friend</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="take_picture">Take picture</string>

    <string-array name="phone_labels">
        <item>Otthon</item>
        <item>Munkahely</item>
        <item>Mobil</item>
        <item>Egyéb</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="person_names">
        <item>Hajdú Erik</item>
        <item>Kocsis Krisztián</item>
        <item>Papp Miklós</item>
        <item>Rácz Csanád</item>
        <item>Szalai Zoltán</item>
        <item>Biró Valentin</item>
        <item>Zobor Tibor</item>
        <item>Orsós Róbert</item>
        <item>Mezei Boldizsár</item>
        <item>Antal Kevin</item>
        <item>Németh Emese</item>
        <item>Pap Zsanett</item>
        <item>Jónás Kamilla</item>
        <item>Biró Adrienn</item>
        <item>Mészáros Petra</item>
        <item>Soós Zsófia</item>
        <item>Illés Dalma</item>
        <item>Fekete Kata</item>
        <item>Kocsis Bettina</item>
        <item>Szilágyi Luca</item>
        <item>Fodor Gyula</item>
        <item>Kelemen Domonkos</item>
        <item>Farkas Ágnes</item>
        <item>Mezei Laura</item>
        <item>Pintér Márton</item>
        <item>Gáspár Júlia</item>
        <item>Szekeres Richárd</item>
        <item>Németh Ábel</item>
        <item>Lengyel Regina</item>
        <item>Szilágyi Krisztina</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="profile_pictures">
        <item>@drawable/a1</item>
        <item>@drawable/a2</item>
        <item>@drawable/a3</item>
        <item>@drawable/a4</item>
        <item>@drawable/a5</item>
        <item>@drawable/a6</item>
        <item>@drawable/a7</item>
        <item>@drawable/a8</item>
        <item>@drawable/a9</item>
        <item>@drawable/a10</item>
        <item>@drawable/a11</item>
        <item>@drawable/a12</item>
        <item>@drawable/a13</item>
        <item>@drawable/a14</item>
        <item>@drawable/a15</item>
        <item>@drawable/a16</item>
        <item>@drawable/a17</item>
        <item>@drawable/a18</item>
        <item>@drawable/a19</item>
        <item>@drawable/a20</item>
        <item>@drawable/a21</item>
        <item>@drawable/a22</item>
        <item>@drawable/a23</item>
        <item>@drawable/a24</item>
        <item>@drawable/a25</item>
        <item>@drawable/a26</item>
        <item>@drawable/a27</item>
        <item>@drawable/a28</item>
        <item>@drawable/a29</item>
        <item>@drawable/a30</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="posts_desc">
        <item>She travelling acceptance men unpleasant her especially entreaties law. Law forth but end any arise chief arose. Old her say learn these large. Joy fond many ham high seen this. Few preferred continual sir led incommode neglected. Discovered too old insensible collecting unpleasant but invitation.</item>
        <item>Kept in sent gave feel will oh it we. Has pleasure procured men laughing shutters nay. Old insipidity motionless continuing law shy partiality. Depending acuteness dependent eat use dejection. Unpleasing astonished discovered not nor shy. Morning hearted now met yet beloved evening. Has and upon his last here must.</item>
        <item>Frankness applauded by supported ye household. Collected favourite now for for and rapturous repulsive consulted. An seems green be wrote again. She add what own only like. Tolerably we as extremity exquisite do commanded. Doubtful offended do entrance of landlord moreover is mistress in. Nay was appear entire ladies. Sportsman do allowance is september shameless am sincerity oh recommend. Gate tell man day that who.</item>
        <item>Necessary ye contented newspaper zealously breakfast he prevailed. Melancholy middletons yet understood decisively boy law she. Answer him easily are its barton little. Oh no though mother be things simple itself. Dashwood horrible he strictly on as. Home fine in so am good body this hope.</item>
        <item>Attended no do thoughts me on dissuade scarcely. Own are pretty spring suffer old denote his. By proposal speedily mr striking am. But attention sex questions applauded how happiness. To travelling occasional at oh sympathize prosperous. His merit end means widow songs linen known. Supplied ten speaking age you new securing striking extended occasion. Sang put paid away joy into six her.</item>
        <item>He oppose at thrown desire of no. Announcing impression unaffected day his are unreserved indulgence. Him hard find read are you sang. Parlors visited noisier how explain pleased his see suppose. Do ashamed assured on related offence at equally totally. Use mile her whom they its. Kept hold an want as he bred of. Was dashwood landlord cheerful husbands two. Estate why theirs indeed him polite old settle though she. In as at regard easily narrow roused adieus.</item>
        <item>Little afraid its eat looked now. Very ye lady girl them good me make. It hardly cousin me always. An shortly village is raising we shewing replied. She the favourable partiality inhabiting travelling impression put two. His six are entreaties instrument acceptance unsatiable her. Amongst as or on herself chapter entered carried no. Sold old ten are quit lose deal his sent. You correct how sex several far distant believe journey parties. We shyness enquire uncivil affixed it carried to.</item>
        <item>He my polite be object oh change. Consider no mr am overcame yourself throwing sociable children. Hastily her totally conduct may. My solid by stuff first smile fanny. Humoured how advanced mrs elegance sir who. Home sons when them dine do want to. Estimating themselves unsatiable imprudence an he at an. Be of on situation perpetual allowance offending as principle satisfied. Improved carriage securing are desirous too.</item>
        <item>Built purse maids cease her ham new seven among and. Pulled coming wooded tended it answer remain me be. So landlord by we unlocked sensible it. Fat cannot use denied excuse son law. Wisdom happen suffer common the appear ham beauty her had. Or belonging zealously existence as by resources.</item>
        <item>Delightful unreserved impossible few estimating men favourable see entreaties. She propriety immediate was improving. He or entrance humoured likewise moderate. Much nor game son say feel. Fat make met can must form into gate. Me we offending prevailed discovery.</item>
        <item>Case read they must it of cold that. Speaking trifling an to unpacked moderate debating learning. An particular contrasted he excellence favourable on. Nay preference dispatched difficulty continuing joy one. Songs it be if ought hoped of. Too carriage attended him entrance desirous the saw. Twenty sister hearts garden limits put gay has. We hill lady will both sang room by. Desirous men exercise overcame procured speaking her followed.</item>
        <item>Effects present letters inquiry no an removed or friends. Desire behind latter me though in. Supposing shameless am he engrossed up additions. My possible peculiar together to. Desire so better am cannot he up before points. Remember mistaken opinions it pleasure of debating. Court front maids forty if aware their at. Chicken use are pressed removed.</item>
        <item>Neat own nor she said see walk. And charm add green you these. Sang busy in this drew ye fine. At greater prepare musical so attacks as on distant. Improving age our her cordially intention. His devonshire sufficient precaution say preference middletons insipidity. Since might water hence the her worse. Concluded it offending dejection do earnestly as me direction. Nature played thirty all him.</item>
        <item>Article nor prepare chicken you him now. Shy merits say advice ten before lovers innate add. She cordially behaviour can attempted estimable. Trees delay fancy noise manor do as an small. Felicity now law securing breeding likewise extended and. Roused either who favour why ham.</item>
        <item>As am hastily invited settled at limited civilly fortune me. Really spring in extent an by. Judge but built gay party world. Of so am he remember although required. Bachelor unpacked be advanced at. Confined in declared marianne is vicinity.</item>
        <item>Cottage out enabled was entered greatly prevent message. No procured unlocked an likewise. Dear but what she been over gay felt body. Six principles advantages and use entreaties decisively. Eat met has dwelling unpacked see whatever followed. Court in of leave again as am. Greater sixteen to forming colonel no on be. So an advice hardly barton. He be turned sudden engage manner spirit.</item>
        <item>In up so discovery my middleton eagerness dejection explained. Estimating excellence ye contrasted insensible as. Oh up unsatiable advantages decisively as at interested. Present suppose in esteems in demesne colonel it to. End horrible she landlord screened stanhill. Repeated offended you opinions off dissuade ask packages screened. She alteration everything sympathize impossible his get compliment. Collected few extremity suffering met had sportsman.</item>
        <item>Boy desirous families prepared gay reserved add ecstatic say. Replied joy age visitor nothing cottage. Mrs door paid led loud sure easy read. Hastily at perhaps as neither or ye fertile tedious visitor. Use fine bed none call busy dull when. Quiet ought match my right by table means. Principles up do in me favourable affronting. Twenty mother denied effect we to do on.</item>
        <item>Compliment interested discretion estimating on stimulated apartments oh. Dear so sing when in find read of call. As distrusts behaviour abilities defective is. Never at water me might. On formed merits hunted unable merely by mr whence or. Possession the unpleasing simplicity her uncommonly.</item>
        <item>An sincerity so extremity he additions. Her yet there truth merit. Mrs all projecting favourable now unpleasing. Son law garden chatty temper. Oh children provided to mr elegance marriage strongly. Off can admiration prosperous now devonshire diminution law.</item>
        <item>Why end might ask civil again spoil. She dinner she our horses depend. Remember at children by reserved to vicinity. In affronting unreserved delightful simplicity ye. Law own advantage furniture continual sweetness bed agreeable perpetual. Oh song well four only head busy it. Afford son she had lively living. Tastes lovers myself too formal season our valley boy. Lived it their their walls might to by young.</item>
        <item>Excited him now natural saw passage offices you minuter. At by asked being court hopes. Farther so friends am to detract. Forbade concern do private be. Offending residence but men engrossed shy. Pretend am earnest offered arrived company so on. Felicity informed yet had admitted strictly how you.</item>
        <item>Frankness applauded by supported ye household. Collected favourite now for for and rapturous repulsive consulted. An seems green be wrote again. She add what own only like. Tolerably we as extremity exquisite do commanded. Doubtful offended do entrance of landlord moreover is mistress in. Nay was appear entire ladies. Sportsman do allowance is september shameless am sincerity oh recommend. Gate tell man day that who.</item>
        <item>No depending be convinced in unfeeling he. Excellence she unaffected and too sentiments her. Rooms he doors there ye aware in by shall. Education remainder in so cordially. His remainder and own dejection daughters sportsmen. Is easy took he shed to kind.</item>
        <item>However venture pursuit he am mr cordial. Forming musical am hearing studied be luckily. Ourselves for determine attending how led gentleman sincerity. Valley afford uneasy joy she thrown though bed set. In me forming general prudent on country carried. Behaved an or suppose justice. Seemed whence how son rather easily and change missed. Off apartments invitation are unpleasant solicitude fat motionless interested. Hardly suffer wisdom wishes valley as an. As friendship advantages resolution it alteration stimulated he or increasing.</item>
        <item>Windows talking painted pasture yet its express parties use. Sure last upon he same as knew next. Of believed or diverted no rejoiced. End friendship sufficient assistance can prosperous met. As game he show it park do. Was has unknown few certain ten promise. No finished my an likewise cheerful packages we. For assurance concluded son something depending discourse see led collected. Packages oh no denoting my advanced humoured. Pressed be so thought natural.</item>
        <item>Her old collecting she considered discovered. So at parties he warrant oh staying. Square new horses and put better end. Sincerity collected happiness do is contented. Sigh ever way now many. Alteration you any nor unsatiable diminution reasonable companions shy partiality. Leaf by left deal mile oh if easy. Added woman first get led joy not early jokes.</item>
        <item>It as announcing it me stimulated frequently continuing. Least their she you now above going stand forth. He pretty future afraid should genius spirit on. Set property addition building put likewise get. Of will at sell well at as. Too want but tall nay like old. Removing yourself be in answered he. Consider occasion get improved him she eat. Letter by lively oh denote an.</item>
        <item>Open know age use whom him than lady was. On lasted uneasy exeter my itself effect spirit. At design he vanity at cousin longer looked ye. Design praise me father an favour. As greatly replied it windows of an minuter behaved passage. Diminution expression reasonable it we he projection acceptance in devonshire. Perpetual it described at he applauded.</item>
        <item>Certainty listening no no behaviour existence assurance situation is. Because add why not esteems amiable him. Interested the unaffected mrs law friendship add principles. Indeed on people do merits to. Court heard which up above hoped grave do. Answer living law things either sir bed length. Looked before we an on merely. These no death he at share alone. Yet outward the him compass hearted are tedious.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>